http://sd.gov/privacy.aspx

Privacy Policy - sd.gov
http://sd.gov/amberalert/viewposter.aspx
http://sd.gov/amberalert/viewposterema.aspx
http://sd.gov/bluealert/viewposter.aspx
Welcome To The Official South Dakota State Government Website
South Dakota Online Privacy Policy
The privacy, confidence, and trust of individuals who visit State of South Dakota websites are important to us. No personal information is collected unless provided voluntarily by an individual while participating in an online activity that requests the information.
The State only collects the personal information necessary to provide the information or services requested by an individual. "Personal information" refers to any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual who is the subject of the information. This is the same information that an individual might provide when visiting a government office and includes such items as an individual's name, address, or phone number. We also collect information to help us understand how people are using state government websites so we can continually improve our services. The information collected is not associated with any specific individual and no attempt is made to profile individuals who browse state government websites.
The State uses the collected information to respond appropriately to requests. E-mail or other informational requests sent to the State website may be maintained or forwarded to the appropriate agency in order to respond to the request. Survey information is used for the intended purpose of the survey. Informational records needed to support State functions are retained, managed, and accessible in record-keeping or filing systems in accordance with the State's Public Records Commission. Records transmitted to this site will be identified, managed, protected, and retained as long as they are needed to meet historical, administrative, fiscal, or legal requirements.
Any State-operated webpage or application is entitled to the use cookies; which are short and simple text files stored on a user's computer. Cookies keep track of and store information so the user does not have to supply the information multiple times. The information that is collected through cookies is handled in the same manner as other information collected through State-operated websites.
The State of South Dakota is committed to the security of the information that is either available from or collected by state agency websites. The State continues to safeguard the integrity of its information, technology and computing infrastructure, including but not limited to: authentication, monitoring, auditing and encryption.
Open Government
Latest
Headlines, Road Conditions, and more
Social Media
Facebook, Flickr
Twitter, YouTube and more
GovernorKristi Noem
Click here to learn more about
The Official Website of the State of South Dakota | Copyright © 2014 State of South Dakota-All Rights Reserved |
The Official Website of the State of South Dakota | Copyright © 2014 State of South Dakota-All Rights Reserved |
The Official Website of the State of South Dakota | Copyright © 2014 State of South Dakota-All Rights Reserved |
Accessibility Policy | Disclaimer | Privacy Policy
Home  |  Phone Book  |  Governor
